# Ivan Reshetar

## Senior Software Engineer

Advanced Software Engineer with more than 10 years of experience in structuring, developing, and implementing interactive solutions. Development is not just my job, it's my passion.

Also, I like to play electronic piano and make new melodies.

## **Work History**

## 2022-07 **-** 2023-09

## Senior Software Engineer

Snapcommerce Inc. – technological company that helps people build credit, save money and travel more. Location: Toronto, ON, Canada.

#### **Achievements:**

- Shipped major features that increased the customer conversion rate to 14%.
- Mentored intern and junior engineers.
- Held technical interviews.
- Prepared technical documentation.

### Used technologies:

React, Redux, Typescript, JavaScript, Node.js, React Native, Next.js, Python, PostgreSQL, Redis, Jest, Enzyme, React Testing Library, Zustand, Microservices, Docker, Datadog, Material UI, Git, Jira, Gitlab, AWS, Cloud Services, Amplitude, WebDriver.

# 2019-07 **-** 2022-05

## Senior Frontend Engineer

Flybits Inc. - product leader in context-aware digital solutions for the financial industry.

Location: Toronto, ON, Canada.

#### Achievements:

- Migrated core company's web product from EmberJS to React. The new React project was built from scratch.
- Developed a new concept of the main product and presented it to senior management. My concept was included in the company's product development roadmap.
- Supervised the development and deployment of key product functionality.

#### Used technologies:

React, Redux, Typescript, JavaScript, EmberJS, Thunk, Styled Components, HTML, CircleCI, Git, NPM, Eslint, AWS, Cloud Services, Docker, Jira.

### Contact

#### Location

Toronto, Ontario, Canada

#### **Phone**

+1(416)-573-45-01

#### E-mail

ivanreshetar@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ivan-reshetar-90b82556/

## **Skills**

React, TypeScript, Node.js,
React Native, JavaScript,
Redux, Zustand, CSS, SCSS,
HTML, PHP, Python, MySQL,
PostgreSQL, MongoDB,
Redis, ORM, Prisma,
GraphQL, Microservices,
Docker, CircleCl, GitHub,
BitBucket, GitLab, Jira,
AWS, Cloud Solutions, Jest,
Enzyme, Puppeteer

## Languages

English



Ukrainian



## 2018-12 - Senior Frontend Engineer

**2019-06** APTN - Aboriginal People Television Network.

Location: Winnipeg, MB, Canada.

#### Achievements:

- Created new functionality for mobile applications (iOS and Android) and released new versions of the applications on Google Play and App Store.
- Created script for transferring 8500 videos from one video hosting to another via API.
- Developed script for automated XML-files conversion to SCV-format.
- Developed 12 micro websites.
- Created new themes and plugins for WordPress websites.

#### Used technologies:

HTML, JavaScript, CSS, jQuery, AJAX, JSON, XML, PHP, MySQL, Ionic, Git, Bitbucket, Agile, Jira.

## 2016-03 - Senior Web Developer

**2018-09** Infocontrol LLC - Copyright protection online-service. Location: Kyiv, Ukraine.

#### **Achievements:**

- New personal cabinet for customers increased conversion in re-sales up to 20%.
- Created from scratch the search engine for searching and analyzing links on other sites.
- Created integration with payment services and customer support services via API.
- Database optimization allowed to increase query processing speed.

#### Used technologies:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, JSON, PHP, MySQL, NodeJS, Express, Git, Bitbucket.

## 2013-12 - Web Developer

**2016-03** Uzhnet LLC - Local Internet Provider.

Location: Uzhhorod, Ukraine.

#### Achievements:

- The introduction of recurrent payments gave an increase in profits up to 18%.
- Developed the billing system for customers.
- Created a system for automatic management and monitoring of network devices (routers, switches).

#### **Used technologies:**

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, JSON, PHP, MySQL, Git.

## **Education**

2014-09 - 2015-12	State University of Telecommunications (Kyiv, Ukraine) Electronics and Telecommunications Engineer (master's degree).
2000-09 - 2005-06	Uzhhorod State University (Uzhhorod, Ukraine) Master of Law (master's degree)
1988-09 - 1999-06	High School (Svalyava, Ukraine)

## Certifications

2017-07	Web Development for Advanced
2018-04	The Complete Web Developer in 2018: Zero to Mastery
2019-11	The Complete Junior to Senior Web Developer Roadmap (2019)
2019-06	Modern React with Redux [2019 Update]
2019-12	Complete React Developer in 2020 (w/ Redux, Hooks, GraphQL)
2020-03	Amazon EC2 Masterclass (Auto Scaling & Load Balancer)
2021-03	JavaScript Security V2
2022-02	The complete app design course - UX, UI and Design thinking
2022-10	Complete Python Developer in 2022
2023-05	JavaScript: The Advanced Concepts